<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on therealplato.com</title>
    <link>http://therealplato.com/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on therealplato.com</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2017 23:18:07 +1300</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://therealplato.com/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>#soberoctober day 12: finishing timez</title>
      <link>http://therealplato.com/posts/soberoctober12/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2017 23:18:07 +1300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://therealplato.com/posts/soberoctober12/</guid>
      <description>Nothing special to report, I spent the evening improving yesterday&amp;rsquo;s timez project.
I split up my complicated parse() function, added many testcases, added some new aliases and formatting strings, loaded local timezones from ~/.timezrc or date binary, and added docs.
I was tickled to see it work across DST boundaries:
content/posts Ω timez UTC at 2017-09-24 02:59:00 Pacific/Auckland UTC: 2017-09-23 14:59:00 content/posts Ω timez UTC at 2017-09-24 03:01:00 Pacific/Auckland UTC: 2017-09-23 14:01:00  I did it for me, but I&amp;rsquo;d love to hear if you also find github.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>#soberoctober day 11: CLI timezone conversion</title>
      <link>http://therealplato.com/posts/soberoctober11/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2017 22:12:35 +1300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://therealplato.com/posts/soberoctober11/</guid>
      <description>Movio has offices in US, UK, DE, NZ and has clients globally. I frequently find myself asking &amp;ldquo;Is it office hours in the US? Is it the middle of the night in Asia?&amp;rdquo; We keep records with UTC timestamps (as all programmers should!) but it&amp;rsquo;s still difficult to conceptualize and mentally convert timezones.
In the past, I&amp;rsquo;ve used several helpful tools:
 The excellent timeanddate.com converter gives you multiple zones and the ability to type or drag to set any zone to any time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>#soberoctober day 10: svg ftw (edit: not yet)</title>
      <link>http://therealplato.com/posts/soberoctober10/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2017 21:27:08 +1300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://therealplato.com/posts/soberoctober10/</guid>
      <description>Long day today, leaving me with no time to dive deep into SVG Animations by Sarah Drasner (O&amp;rsquo;Reilly). Copyright 2017 Sarah Drasner, 978-1-491-93970-3.
Let&amp;rsquo;s see what I can get done with an hour and some lipsum&amp;hellip;
 &amp;hellip; Not very far. My objective was to make an arrow that starts pointing down and animates to point up as you scroll down the page.
After conceding that was not a newbie task, I just looped the animation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>#soberoctober day 9: blender looks easy amirite</title>
      <link>http://therealplato.com/posts/soberoctober09/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Oct 2017 21:42:44 +1300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://therealplato.com/posts/soberoctober09/</guid>
      <description>Today&amp;rsquo;s project: Make a 3D Printable STL file!
I don&amp;rsquo;t have a 3D printer but a colleague just got one and has kindly offered to collaborate if I give him an STL.
I know that&amp;rsquo;s a filetype of 3D models but I&amp;rsquo;ve never made one. Time to figure it out.
Inkscape  Learned to trace a rastered image into svg by placing and modifying bezier curve handles Learned to set fill of a closed path (took an embarrassingly long time)  Blender  Learned to set an object&amp;rsquo;s pivot center Learned to import and extrude an SVG Learned to convert curve to mesh Learned the boolean difference modifier Learned what a &amp;ldquo;non-manifold mesh&amp;rdquo; is (but not how to fix it) Learned that some 3D printers consider Y axis to be vertical  Figuring out the above and producing this stl took ~3 hours.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>#soberoctober day 8: interplanetary file system</title>
      <link>http://therealplato.com/posts/soberoctober08/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Oct 2017 21:17:55 +1300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://therealplato.com/posts/soberoctober08/</guid>
      <description>This evening I set up the Interplanetary File System and uploaded the first episode of Reality Exploit Roundtable, a 2012 podcast I helped create.
It was really straightforward:
go get -u -d github.com/ipfs/go-ipfs cd $GOPATH/src/github.com/ipfs/go-ipfs make install ipfs init ipfs daemon #in other term ipfs add ~/Downloads/realityexploitroundtable-EP001.ogg # added QmdPt2EqonqKcwyxbuePuiwPsEc8c3t5R3Dr4oTDBpUmXM realityexploitroundtable-EP001.ogg  Tada! That&amp;rsquo;s that, my file is now in a global p2p filesystem. Actually, &amp;ldquo;global&amp;rdquo; is a misnomer - it&amp;rsquo;s named &amp;ldquo;interplanetary&amp;rdquo; because the project aims to be usable for syncing content between Earth and Mars and beyond, and is designed to work within bandwidth and latency constraints.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>#soberoctober day 7: one of us</title>
      <link>http://therealplato.com/posts/soberoctober07/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Oct 2017 18:26:49 +1300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://therealplato.com/posts/soberoctober07/</guid>
      <description>Today&amp;rsquo;s societies are impersonal behemoths. Our governments attempt to apply identical rules to millions or billions of people with very different lives, and our media and education systems help by reinforcing expected patterns of behavior.
I&amp;rsquo;ve deleted paragraphs from this post out of fear that society at large would punish me for sharing those bits of information. I&amp;rsquo;m not sure if those bits would result in legal consequences; if they would trigger individuals to dox, swat or DDOS me; or if no one would care.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>#soberoctober day 6: 剁椒鱼头BBQ</title>
      <link>http://therealplato.com/posts/soberoctober06/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2017 21:21:27 +1300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://therealplato.com/posts/soberoctober06/</guid>
      <description>One Friday per month, Movio has a barbecue, with responsibility rotating among squads. Today it was Red Squad&amp;rsquo;s turn and it was good.
My squadmate Gary planned the menu and was chief grillmaster. Following his recipes, we made green bean stuffed chicken wings, fish head chili, fish fillets, omelettes, handmade noodles, and egg-free vegan noodles. Our product owner Vlad also made fried halloumi, sausages and regular chicken wings as backup dishes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>#soberoctober day 5:  JIT</title>
      <link>http://therealplato.com/posts/soberoctober05/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2017 23:55:00 +1300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://therealplato.com/posts/soberoctober05/</guid>
      <description>document.addEventListener(&#34;DOMContentLoaded&#34;, function() { $.get(&#34;https://5b567rkzxe.execute-api.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/prod/com-therealplato-counter?TableName=com-therealplato-counter&#34;, function(data, status){ if(status != &#34;success&#34;) { return } $(&#34;#counter-button&#34;).text(data.m) }) $(&#34;#counter-button&#34;).click(function(){ $.post(&#34;https://5b567rkzxe.execute-api.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/prod/com-therealplato-counter?TableName=com-therealplato-counter&#34;, {}, function(data, status){ if(status != &#34;success&#34;) { return } $(&#34;#counter-button&#34;).text(data.m) }); }); })  I barely completed this by midnight! AWS is complicated. This button hits an AWS API Gateway, which proxies to a lambda function, which reads and/or updates dynamodb:
Button has been clicked&amp;nbsp;&amp;hellip;&amp;nbsp;times
Arch Of The Day While trying to use two finger scrolling, I observed this entertaining behavior:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>#soberoctober day 4: a bit of serverless</title>
      <link>http://therealplato.com/posts/soberoctober04/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2017 19:34:11 +1300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://therealplato.com/posts/soberoctober04/</guid>
      <description>Today&amp;rsquo;s Achievements: I tried Amazon Lambda. I first heard of this &amp;ldquo;serverless&amp;rdquo; computing at Full Stack Fest 2016. You give Amazon a function and only pay for resources used as the function runs. I immediately observed that there are, in fact, still servers involved, you&amp;rsquo;re just delegating operations to Amazon.
After I got over my pedantry and listened to this story I decided I liked the idea. Lambda can be orders of magnitudes cheaper than EC2 (for sporadic resource use,) or more expensive than EC2 (for pegged resource use.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>#soberoctober day 3: blog it</title>
      <link>http://therealplato.com/posts/soberoctober03/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Oct 2017 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://therealplato.com/posts/soberoctober03/</guid>
      <description> Started the day off with 50 kettlebell swings, will keep it up till Monday, when I&amp;rsquo;ll increase to 100.
A colleague has joined the #soberoctober challenge.
Today&amp;rsquo;s achievements:  Learned how SPF works Deployed this blog to therealplato.github.io and therealplato.com Earned &amp;ldquo;Banker&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;Thermalist&amp;rdquo; awards in Terraforming Mars, didn&amp;rsquo;t win  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>#soberoctober day 2: out with the mold</title>
      <link>http://therealplato.com/posts/soberoctober02/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Oct 2017 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://therealplato.com/posts/soberoctober02/</guid>
      <description>Keep catching myself reaching for my e-cig, locked far away. Bought seven types of gum to try instead. &amp;ldquo;5 Watermelon&amp;rdquo; package indicates eating the whole pack results in a laxative effect, neat! Considered buying some nicotine-free ecig liquid but that feels like cheating&amp;hellip;
Today&amp;rsquo;s Achievements  Doused my moldy bedframe in sodium hydroxide Found and threw out a moldy spare pillow Yoga: for the first time in Downward Dog I touched my heels to the ground Set up Hugo and compiled these first posts from markdown  Arch, worth its own section&amp;hellip;  Got my brightness function keys working thanks to jmesmon/illum Learned how to close windows with awesome (default super-shift-c) Learned how to throw windows around workspaces (super-shift-2), switch workspaces, (super-2), reflow workspace (super-space) Learned why firefox was covering up all my other windows - I hit super-T instead of ctrl-T, making awesome &amp;ldquo;keep on Top&amp;rdquo;  Arch wishlist:  Show bandwidth use, wifi state, battery level in system tray Make my clock update DST automatically.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>#soberoctober day 1: challenge accepted</title>
      <link>http://therealplato.com/posts/soberoctober01/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Oct 2017 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://therealplato.com/posts/soberoctober01/</guid>
      <description>Wut? Joe Rogan Experience #1007 introduced the Sober October challenge. I realized I couldn&amp;rsquo;t remember the last time I went a week without a beer. I&amp;rsquo;m certainly dependent on nicotine, I wonder if I am dependent on alcohol? Let&amp;rsquo;s find out.
Goal: Produce something useful each day this month instead of getting drunk and sucking at rocket league.
Rules: Caffiene is allowed.
Every other psychoactive substance is disallowed including nicotine and alcohol.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>